[{"success": true, "timeout": false, "failed_images": [], "failed_audio": [], "failed_video": [], "trial_type": "preload", "trial_index": 0, "time_elapsed": 379, "internal_node_id": "0.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 3098, "stimulus": ["<p> Welcome! </p> <p> We are conducting an experiment about how people evaluate intuitive physics situations when asked a question in plain english. Your answers will be used to inform computer science and cognitive science research.</p><p> This experiment should take no more than <strong>10 minutes</strong></p> <p>  Press any key to begin. </p>"], "response": "enter", "trial_type": "html-keyboard-response", "trial_index": 1, "time_elapsed": 3479, "internal_node_id": "0.0-1.0"}, {"rt": 2, "stimulus": ["<p>In this experiment, you will be presented with a series of images containing <strong>stacks of blocks and some simple questions.</strong></p><p>The block are stacked on a grey platform in a configuration which may or may not be stable.</p><p>In each situation, you will be asked to imagine what will occur after a sufficiently large amount of time has passed and gravity has finished acting on the stacks of blocks.", "<p>Your task will be to think about how these blocks will fall and their position <strong>after they have finished falling</strong>. Note that sometimes, you may be presented with a stable stack where no blocks will fall.<p>You will enter your answer for each question by clicking a rating on a <strong>7-point multiple choice scale</strong> ranging from <strong>1 (definitely no)</strong> to <strong>7 (definitely yes)</strong>.", "<p>You will see descriptions of <strong>24  different scenarios</strong> in total.</p><p> When you are ready, please click any key to complete a quick comprehension check, before moving on to the experiment. </p>"], "response": "shift", "trial_type": "html-keyboard-response", "trial_index": 2, "time_elapsed": 3482, "internal_node_id": "0.0-2.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 65139, "response": {"Q0": "Look at images containing blocks and answer questions about what is currently occuring in the image.", "Q1": "By selecting an option from a multiple choice scale."}, "question_order": [0, 1], "trial_type": "survey-multi-choice", "trial_index": 3, "time_elapsed": 68625, "internal_node_id": "0.0-2.0-1.0"}, {"rt": 11695, "stimulus": ["<p>In this experiment, you will be presented with a series of images containing <strong>stacks of blocks and some simple questions.</strong></p><p>The block are stacked on a grey platform in a configuration which may or may not be stable.</p><p>In each situation, you will be asked to imagine what will occur after a sufficiently large amount of time has passed and gravity has finished acting on the stacks of blocks.", "<p>Your task will be to think about how these blocks will fall and their position <strong>after they have finished falling</strong>. Note that sometimes, you may be presented with a stable stack where no blocks will fall.<p>You will enter your answer for each question by clicking a rating on a <strong>7-point multiple choice scale</strong> ranging from <strong>1 (definitely no)</strong> to <strong>7 (definitely yes)</strong>.", "<p>You will see descriptions of <strong>24  different scenarios</strong> in total.</p><p> When you are ready, please click any key to complete a quick comprehension check, before moving on to the experiment. </p>"], "response": "enter", "trial_type": "html-keyboard-response", "trial_index": 4, "time_elapsed": 80327, "internal_node_id": "0.0-2.1-0.1"}, {"rt": 11809, "response": {"Q0": "Look at images containing blocks and answer questions about what will happen in the image after gravity has acted on the blocks.", "Q1": "By selecting an option from a multiple choice scale."}, "question_order": [0, 1], "trial_type": "survey-multi-choice", "trial_index": 5, "time_elapsed": 92138, "internal_node_id": "0.0-2.1-1.1"}, {"rt": 25624, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "42", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 6, "time_elapsed": 117769, "internal_node_id": "0.0-3.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 11128, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "13", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 7, "time_elapsed": 128903, "internal_node_id": "0.0-4.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 14877, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "46", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 8, "time_elapsed": 143787, "internal_node_id": "0.0-5.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 43162, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "14", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 9, "time_elapsed": 186955, "internal_node_id": "0.0-6.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 19047, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "47", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 10, "time_elapsed": 206007, "internal_node_id": "0.0-7.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 13826, "response": {"Q0": 3}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "4", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "26", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 11, "time_elapsed": 219839, "internal_node_id": "0.0-8.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 25467, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "8", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 12, "time_elapsed": 245312, "internal_node_id": "0.0-9.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 8191, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will most of the blocks have stayed on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "45", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 13, "time_elapsed": 253509, "internal_node_id": "0.0-10.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 18182, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "41", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 14, "time_elapsed": 271696, "internal_node_id": "0.0-11.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 11999, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "10", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 15, "time_elapsed": 283701, "internal_node_id": "0.0-12.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7142, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "40", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 16, "time_elapsed": 290848, "internal_node_id": "0.0-13.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 10985, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "12", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 17, "time_elapsed": 301839, "internal_node_id": "0.0-14.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 9836, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "3", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "19", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 18, "time_elapsed": 311681, "internal_node_id": "0.0-15.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 17914, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "5", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "36", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 19, "time_elapsed": 329601, "internal_node_id": "0.0-16.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 18577, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "5", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 20, "time_elapsed": 348184, "internal_node_id": "0.0-17.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 12927, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "16", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 21, "time_elapsed": 361117, "internal_node_id": "0.0-18.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 4815, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "37", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 22, "time_elapsed": 365937, "internal_node_id": "0.0-19.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 11488, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "2", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 23, "time_elapsed": 377430, "internal_node_id": "0.0-20.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 195485, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "44", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 24, "time_elapsed": 572920, "internal_node_id": "0.0-21.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 9449, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "18", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 25, "time_elapsed": 582374, "internal_node_id": "0.0-22.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 5123, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "3", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "24", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 26, "time_elapsed": 587502, "internal_node_id": "0.0-23.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 6004, "response": {"Q0": 4}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "1", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 27, "time_elapsed": 593512, "internal_node_id": "0.0-24.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 1484, "response": {"Q0": ""}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "4", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 28, "time_elapsed": 595000, "internal_node_id": "0.0-25.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 13720, "response": {"Q0": 2}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "5", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "35", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 29, "time_elapsed": 608726, "internal_node_id": "0.0-26.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 81955, "response": {"Q0": "7", "Q1": "6", "Q2": "I kind of thought about the game jenga and what I would expect to happen there", "Q3": ""}, "trial_type": "survey-text", "trial_index": 30, "time_elapsed": 690701, "internal_node_id": "0.0-27.0"}]